LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
The boat and the cyborg floats are at this address.
Still, what do you plan to do
with this handful of weapons?
I'm pushing for refugee liberation.
Damn, I feel for them.
Well, not that I care, as long as I get paid.
Receipt of Goods
1702 Automatic Rifle x 200
18 Recoilless Anti-Tank Cannon x 22
Grenade x 180
Gunship x 4
Jetskis x 8
Portable Missile Launcher x 15
Cyborg Floats x 48
Hey, what's this?
Right on schedule.
Dammit.
Hey!
You bastard! You sold us out, didn't you?!
Rhapsody
The Melody
of a
Bygone Nation
How is the ID check going on the high-spec male
cyborg who tried to kill the Prime Minister?
We've been looking, focusing on military personnel,
but we haven't got any hits yet.
After that helicopter went
out of control a while back,
the military seriously upgraded their security.
About that high-spec cyborg...
Note: PKF = Peace Keeping Force
the only existing record shows that deployed
PKF troops were equipped with this build.
Strangely, not only has the PKF's member list
disappeared, but also their operation records.
So, it's a maintenance-free
PKF-spec model.
Togusa, what about the organisation that was supposedly
involved in the nuclear power plant in Shinjuku?
I haven't found anything
concrete about that, either.
A new public agency that emerged
after the new cabinet was established,
not to mention one with members who
are well-connected with the SDF...
Eleven out-of-control helicopters...
The Individual Eleven,
who began to appear as if to echo that incident...
The nuclear power plant facility that was
secreted away underground in Shinjuku...
We have a whole lot of problems to deal with.
I heard that the Chief was called
to the Prime Minister's office again
in regards to "something" that
was dug up at that power plant.
Yes, he was; is there something
you don't like about that?
A whole lot.
Don't you think this is all
screwed up to begin with?
If I remember correctly, Section 9 is an organisation
that goes on the offensive against crime.
But if we're going to be held
down by the scruff of our necks,
we sure as hell can't take any preemptive actions.
I won't argue with you,
and I'm sure the Chief feels the same way.
Then, why...
What is our greatest enemy?
What do you mean?
The answer is... numbers.
In particular, in the face of an enemy
with strong numerical superiority,
organisations such as Section 9
will be powerless and suffer defeat.
If this current situation is
in itself an attack on us...
is it not possible to think that something is
starting to happen elsewhere, unbeknownst to us?
You are aware that a plutonium
fuel rod was recovered
during an operation to re-bury the underground
nuclear power plant in Shinjuku, yes?
I have heard of it, yes.
A plan was formulated to secretly
transport the fuel rod to safety,
but it was leaked to terrorists
before it could be executed.
"We intend to enact divine
punishment upon the government,
which has committed an act of folly
under the very feet of the refugees,
who await liberation as new citizens."
"We believe that returning what
has been dug up by refugees,
in the land of the refugees, to the refugees themselves
is the only reasonable and proper course of action."
"The Individual Eleven."
That symbol's on there, too.
After that declaration arrived,
the Coast Guard interrupted a weapons deal,
but there is a possibility that a large
amount of weaponry had already been sold.
The original plan was to
transport the fuel rod by sea.
However, a receipt left behind by the
terrorists led us to expect an attack at sea,
so there has been a change in plans.
So, the new plan is to have Section
9 transport the fuel rod by land?
That is correct.
Section 9 does not officially exist.
In other words, it is an ideal agency to employ
as a means of transporting a pre-war relic
that isn't supposed to exist in the first place.
I see.
And what is your opinion on this
matter, Prime Minister?
I believe the decision is... appropriate.
Understood.
Prime Minister, if I may ask one question?
What is it?
To what extent were you aware of
the nuclear power plant in Shinjuku?
I first learned of its existence
when the plutonium was found.
I see.
Excuse me.
The operation's details are
as previously reviewed.
We will use ground transport to move the plutonium
fuel rod from the residential refugee sector.
What's going on?
As I thought, the excavation was a secret operation under
government supervision. If so, then why did you...
Old man...
Since when did Section 9 become
the Prime Minister's errand boy?
We haven't switched roles.
Then...
It just means that someone else
beat us to the first move.
Isn't that right, Chief?
You're...
We meet again.
I am quite relieved to hear that you
will accompany me on my first drop.
What are you doing here?
Not to mention that you're saying you're "with" us?
My sentiments exactly.
To think that I got hauled out here to supervise
the cleanup of such a worthless wartime relic...
Why me? It's infuriating, really.
Hi there. Thanks for the other day.
Who is he?
Cabinet Intelligence Agency, Investigative
Council for Possible Changes to Wartime Strategy,
Representative Aide, Gouda Kazundo.
Gouda: What an awful job this is.
So that's who he is...
Commander, it appears that the recovery
team has departed Niihama as scheduled.
I see. I hope nothing goes wrong.
I hope so, too.
Here.
Like monkeys in a zoo, aren't they?
Stop that.
Don't say things that might provoke them.
If they cross the fence,
they'll either be shot to death or deported.
Even they understand that much.
Then, does that mean the on-site SDF were not
even made aware of what they were protecting?
That is correct.
There are many things in this world
that one does not need to know.
In order to manipulate information with
efficiency after the operation is complete,
it is desirable to have a minimal
number of people know the truth.
If that's the case, why didn't the Cabinet Intelligence
Agency conduct this entire operation in the first place?!
Not to mention...
Togusa!
I believe this is the first time we've met...
Have we met before somewhere...?
Ishikawa.
Yeah, we'll arrive soon.
Saitou, Pazu, Bomer;
once you acquire the truck,
rendezvous with the team at 2200 hours.
Roger.
Take Tachikoma as well.
I must ask that you not use the
sentient tanks in this mission.
Bastard...!
I wish to avoid provoking the refugees.
Mr. Gouda.
I understand that you are fully
in charge of this operation,
but I will have you follow our orders on-site.
Otherwise, we cannot guarantee your safety.
I will have you drop in tandem with Batou.
I'll be counting on you.
I'll be dropping first!
Now then, shall we get going?
I'm not very fond of things like this.
Well, how nice for you.
All right, go!
No time to waste; let's roll!
I've been in a cold sweat ever
since I heard this was plutonium.
You've done well.
We'll take over and transport this
out of the residential refugee sector.
Negative.
After all, my subordinates
may have been irradiated.
Don't worry, such concern is unnecessary.
What would a bureaucrat know about it?
You may despise bureaucrats all you
like, but this is government policy.
Each section has a designated function.
If you dislike that fact, take off your uniform.
However, I'm sure that it will not put you at ease.
So, I have a favour to ask of you...
I'll tell you over a closed-circuit link.
Hey!
Don't worry. It's just a bureaucrat
doing his job: cleaning up a mess.
Commander, the transport vehicle has arrived.
Understood.
An XO and a Private from our
ranks will accompany you.
That is the concession.
Affirmative. We will depart as soon
as we finish reinforcing the vehicle.
All right, we're moving out!
It's somehow unnerving.
We can't rule out the possibility that the
Individual Eleven may have a hijacking planned,
but it's not as though they have a
firm partnership with the refugees.
Be careful, but don't get paranoid.
You're right.
I'm more worried about where the leak of
the previous sea-route plans came from.
True enough.
If it becomes known that plutonium is on this bus,
they'll be very surprised, I'm sure.
Cut the lame chitchat.
Sorry. Unlike you people,
I live by this "chitchat".
How innocent.
Hey, have you heard of this?
In Nagasaki's residential refugee sector,
a girl about her age fired on a policeman.
What's the point in trying to make us nervous?
It seems your team members have
undergone extensive training.
Your female commander is frightening, too.
Not as much as you think.
Oh? Why did you join Section 9 under her command?
Could it be that you have feelings for her?
Surely not, eh?
What a joker.
Ishikawa, how is the route recon going?
I'll send you data from the satellite.
The road becomes elevated ahead.
Isn't that dangerous?
Once you reach the old highway,
you'll have exited the refugee sector.
Soon after that, we'll be done, when we hand over
the package to the receiver from Yokosuka base.
The perimeter highway is more dangerous, actually.
The majority of the buildings left in that area lie
collapsed and abandoned; they block both sides of the road.
If the terrorists laid an ambush
there, we won't have a chance.
What a plan.
What is Gouda thinking?
Ishikawa, once you finish making a pass through
the route, try digging into his background.
Yeah, I intend to do just that.
It's now thirty years since the last World War.
That they've still done nothing with the Kantou region
is basically the end result of them trying to maintain
ambiguity regarding the refugee problem, right?
Perhaps the issue has reached critical mass.
Hey.
I know.
Batou.
I can see it, too.
I don't like it at all...
Ishikawa, can you see this?
Yeah, could it be an accident that
resulted in an overturned vehicle?
I'm not sure. I'm going to check this out.
If we are to prioritise safety,
the obvious solution would be to take a detour.
Considering our cargo,
we must avoid combat at all costs.
I am well aware of that.
That's why we're camouflaged.
We'll scout this out first.
If the terrorists are waiting for us in
there, we'll just have to be prepared.
Fine.
So, who will go?
Saitou and I.
Batou will assume command here.
All right; I'll go with you.
Even though I may not look
it, I get along with refugees.
I also want one of the GSDF men to come
along; your subordinates are too hostile.
What's the problem?
It's what you see.
Are you from the western district?
Something like that.
We'd like to get going.
So would we.
Sorry, but we don't have time to help.
We'll just be going through.
Whatever.
There's enough room next to the
truck for the bus to pass by.
Go slow, and if you see anything that looks
bad, leave us behind and punch through.
Roger.
Situation normal.
Keep going.
What's this?
Batou.
Yeah.
Reinforcements?
Hey, that guy has a gun.
Togusa, go!
Get on!
Report.
Clear.
Something's wrong...
Were they just refugees?
We killed them needlessly.
Well done.
Information on the armed terrorist
attack appears to have been false.
Fortunately, it was just wasted effort.
Mr. Aramaki, Section 9 did an
excellent job again in this mission.
I am extremely grateful.
Are you being sarcastic, or what?
I mean what I say.
Hey!
Don't!
Bastard! Back there, you...
By now, the GSDF's 2nd Bridging Platoon
will have withdrawn from camp and
sent the plutonium out by sea.
So you used us as a decoy.
Just who the hell do you think we are?!
And who do you think you are?
A small, elite force of top agents?
If you had been attacked by a horde of refugees
who were armed with contraband weapons,
you would've been powerless to stop them.
Be thankful that you even got to play
the decoy role in my production.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
and singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(Our time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
(the time is now)
All the truth,
(All the truth)
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.